

CONTACT

8

Born 1989 in United States



New York, United States



+1 (646) 932-0850



thejohnlima@icloud.com



@thejohnlima github.com/thejohnlima



https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlim

SKILLS

Xcode

Swift

Obj-C

MVVM

.

SPM

Tests

Auto Lavout

Agile Methodologies

JOHN LIMA

IOS DEVELOPER

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept of the ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer iOS Developer - FreeCast Inc Since January 2021

Working with Swift for iOS and tvOS applications

Freelancer iOS Developer - Stormbreaker Studios January 2020 - December 2020

Working in iOS applications using Swift

iOS Developer - PagSeguro UOL Since July 2018

Working with native applications using Swift

iOS Developer - BRQ April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native applications using Swift and Objective-C

iOS Developer - Magna Sistemas

February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native applications using Swift...

EDUCATION

System Analysis and Development

February 2014 - June 2018, Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

iOS Developer